让我们开始我们的项目，并将代码推送到GitHub
Let's take our project and work on pushing the code to GitHub
这样我们就能看到它的能力。
so that we can see what it's capable of.
但首先 我们将讨论一些我们之前在git网站上看到的命令
But 1st, we're going to discuss some of those commands that we saw earlier on the gittub website.
第一个是增加远程代码库。
The 1st was adding remotes.
现在，这个命令通常是git remote add，
Now, the command for this is normally git remote add,
然后是你想要为远程添加的名称然后是你想要放置这个文件的url。
and then the name that you want to add for the remote and then the url where you want to place this file.
将项目连接到GitHub的方法是使用以下Git远程命令建立远程连接。
The way that you connect your project to GitHub is by setting up this remote connection with this Git remote command.
现在您需要传递这个名称以及您希望托管您的repo的URL。
Now you need to pass along this name as well as the URL where you want to host your repo.
你不需要在GitHub上托管它。
You don't have to host it with GitHub.
你可以在其他地方托管它
There are other places where you can host it.
很多时候，您的公司会有一个需要发布代码仓库的地方。
A lot of times, your company will have a place where you need to post your repository.
你使用的远程仓库的一个很常见的名字是Origin
And a very common name for the remote that you're using is Origin.
所以你可以看到你在向原点推进，
So you may see that you're pushing to origin,
你将那个URL分配给原始名称，
and you're assigning that URL to the origin name,
这样你就不用记住URL了，URL不会很长。
so that you don't have to remember the URL, which can't be pretty long.
你可以添加尽可能多的远程位置，
That you can add as many remote locations,
这意味着如果你愿意，你可以把你的工作推到多个地方，
which means that you can push your work to multiple places if you want to,
所以你可以添加多个远程代码库，
so you can add more than one remote,
如果你需要将备份文件推送到其他地方，这有时很有用，
and that's sometimes useful if you need to push to a backup files somewhere else,
以及托管项目的远程。
as well as the remote where your items are hosted.
当然，现在您可以使用git remote删除或重命名远程文件。
Now you can of course, remove or rename the remote with the git remote.
还有git rename命令，你可以看到这里的命令都很有解释性。
And the git rename command, you can see the commands here are pretty solve explanatory.
git remote remove，然后输入要删除的文件名然后git rename。
So git remote remove, and then you say the name that you want to remove and then git rename.
你只需要给它一个新名字和旧名字
You just give it the new name as well as the old name in there.
然后有一个选项来列出远程
And then there is an option to list the remotes.
你可以使用git remote，
You can just use actually git remote,
它会给你所有可用远程代码库的列表，
and it'll just give you the list of all the remotes available,
或者你也可以使用git remote - v选项，- v表示冗长，
or you can also use the git remote minus v option, and minus v means verbose,
它会列出所有的远程代码库，并为它们提供一些额外的信息。
it'll just list all the remotes with a bunch of additional information for them.
您必须知道的另一个命令是如何将内容从本地目录推送到github
The other command that you have to know is how to push things from your local directory into github.
这是用git push命令完成的
That is done with the git push command
push是指将文件从本地机器移动到GitHub的方式
now push is how you move files from the local machine to  GitHub
本地分支必须连接到该分支的远程版本。
And local branches have to be connected to that remote version of the branch.
第一次推的时候，你必须加上-u选项，这是上游选项。
The 1st time you push, you have to add the minus u option, which is the set-upstream-to options.
所以这个“上游-to”是这里-u的加长版。
So this set-upstream-to is the longer version of minus u right here.
然后输入你想要使用的远程代码库的名称，
and then you put the name of the remote that you want to use,
然后是你想要推送的分支你也可以发出git push - - all命令，
and then also the branch that you want to push that you can also issue a git push minus minus all command,
我经常这样做，把你所有的本地分支都推到github上，
which I do often that's going to take all your local branches and push them all into github,
这很方便。
which is pretty convenient.
有时候，当你试图推树枝时，
Now, sometimes when you try to push a branch,
github将要求您手动在github上的分支和本地分支之间建立连接。
github will ask you to make the connection manually between the branch that you have on Gitub and the branch that you have locally.
这两者之间有联系。
There's a link between those.
有时候你需要使用另一个命令git branch set-upstream-to。
And so sometimes you have to use this other command called git branch set-upstream-to.
然后加上origin和远程分支的名称，你就会碰到这个。
and then you add origin and the name of the remote branch, and you'll run into that.
一旦失去连接，它就会告诉你，
It'll just tell you whenever it's lost that connection,
它会给你需要使用的命令，
and it'll actually give you the command that you need to use,
你可以按节奏复制，这很方便。
which you can copy in pace, and that is pretty convenient.
我们来看看能不能把这些连接到GitHub
So let's go ahead and see if we can connect these to GitHub
我们一直在做的工作。我们回到这一页。
the work that we've been doing. We're back on this page right here.
我真正需要从这个页面的唯一东西是我需要添加的远程的url
The only thing I really need from this page is the url of the remote that I need to add
下面的URL与扩展名为.git的代码仓库的URL相同。
that URL down here is the same as the url of the repository with the .git extension.
如果你想记住url，它和常规url是一样的。
So if you ever want to remember the url, it's just the same thing as the regular url.
但是让我们继续从这里复制它 然后回到我们的项目
But let's go ahead and copy it from here, and we'll go back into our project.
我还有一些打开的文件
And I have some open files.
这是从之前的视频中被删除的，
This one from a previous video that's actually deleted,
让我们把这些东西关起来，把自述留着，
so let's go ahead and just close the stuff out, and we'll leave the readme up,
我将开始发出一些这样的命令。
and I'm going to start issuing some of these commands.
我要做的第一件事就是设置好远程代码库，
So the 1st thing I need to do is set up my remote,
所以我要发出一个git remote addorigin，
so I'm gonna issue a git remote add origin,
然后粘贴url，然后使用git push，
and then I'll paste the url, and then I'm going to use git push,
我可以推原点，
and I can just push the origin,
然后我也可以使用git push - - all，这将会推入所有分支。
but then I can also just use git push minus minus all, and this will push all the branches.
现在，我不想向你展示github上的分支是如何出现的，
Now, I don't want to show you how branches appear on github,
这里有几个分支。
so I have a couple of branches here.
这既影响标题分支，也影响主分支。
This affects headline branch as well as the main branch.
所以我想把它们都放到github上，
So I want to go ahead and push them all to github,
它会把它们发送到GitHub，
and it's going to send them to GitHub,
创建这两个新分支，
create these two new branches,
并在当地的分支机构之间建立关系，
and also create the relationships between the branch that is here locally,
以及将被发送到github的分支。
as well as the branch that will be sent to github.
记住您可以使用的另一个命令
so remember the other command that you can use
如果你只想推主分支，就是git push - u。
if you just want to push the main branch, is git push minus u.
这就建立了上游的链接，
That sets up the upstream link,
然后你写入origin main，
and then you would say, origin main,
如果你只是想送其中一个，
if you just want to send one of them,
我通常push所有东西。
I usually just push everything.
这就是我。
That's just me.
让我们把这个清除掉，看看GitHub上的这个页面。
So let's go ahead and clear this out and take a look at this page on GitHub.
我们会刷新这个 因为我们推送了一个提交
We're going to refresh this since we've pushed a commit.
你可以看到我们的文件，
You can see that our documents,
Readme文件许可证，git忽略我们本地拥有的，已经在github上了。
the Readme file license, and git ignore that we had locally, is already on github.
如果你点击这里，
And if you click right here,
你可以看到有多个分支，
you can see that you have multiple branches,
我们推的两个分支，你可以说，
the two branches that we pushed, and you can say,
我想查看这里所有的分支
I want to view all the branches here
看看你所有的分支。
and take a look at any of the branches that you have.
你也可以在这里删除它们，如果你愿意，可以添加分支名称，
You can also delete them here, added the branch names if you want to,
然后创建拉取请求，我们会讲到
and create something called pull requests, which we will get to
我点击这里回到我的主文件夹。
So I'm going to click back here to go back into my main folder.
还有很多其他的信息我会在下个视频中讲到
And there's all kinds of other information which I want to go to in the next video.
但是推送第一个代码仓库 第一次做的时候不会很兴奋
But pushing that 1st repository, it can't be really exciting the 1st time you do it.
但是GitHub要求这么多选项，这可能有点令人生畏。
But GitHub asked so many options that it could be a little bit daunting.
我将在下个视频中讨论所有这些选项
I'll go over all those options in the next video.